Guide to the International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences Records 1970-1984
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence, Papers and Registration Materials
  - Registration, A, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - A-ACH, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - ACI-ADA, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - ADO-AHM, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - AIT-ALV, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - AMA-ANT, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - ANT-ARE, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - ARE-ALE, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - AL-ATHE, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Adams, Richard N., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Albert, Ethel, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - American Indians, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Ananti, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Andersen, Raoul, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Andersen, Raoul, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Araki, Hiroyuki, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Arens, W., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Armstrong, R.D., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Arnott, Margarett, 1972-1976 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Aschenbrenner, Joyce and Lloyd Collins, from the conference, "The developmental process of urbanism," 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Aschenbrenner, Joyce and Lloyd Collins, from the conference, "The developmental process of urbanism," 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Ayad, B., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Address, B, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Congress Service Corps, B, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Registration, B, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - BAB-BAN, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - BANG-BAR, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - BART-BATH, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - BAU-BED, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - BEFU-BEN, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - BENN-BHO, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - BHU-BIN, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - BIRN-BOI, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - BOL-BOS, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - BOST-BRE, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - BREM-BRO, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - BRO-BUC, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - BUD-BYE, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Ballesti, T., photographs, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Banks, David, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Baradon, A., 1974 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Bansal, I.J.S., 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Barraclough, S., 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Bascom, Wm., 1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Belcove, Janet Seca and Allan, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Ben-Ami, I. 1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Berdichewsky, Bernardo, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Bernardi, Bernardo, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Bharti, A., 1974-1976 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Bhowmik, K.L., 1973 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Blacking, John, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Bokongo, S., 1973 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Bornkamp, Ari, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Bratanic, Branimir, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Bratanic, Branimir, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Bronley, Yu.V., 1975 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Browman, David L., June-Dec, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Browman, David L., Jan-May, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Browman, David L., 1974 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Brues, Alice, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Bryce, R.S., 1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Burger, Henry, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Burnett, J., 1972 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Butzer, Elizabeth, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Address, C, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Congress Service Corps, C, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Registration, C, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - C, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - CAB-CAR, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - CARE-CER, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - CHA-CHI, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - CHI-CL, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - CLAIR-COL, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - COLL-CONG, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - CONK-COR, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - COR-CZ, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Calhoun, C., and Ianni, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Camino, D.C. A., 1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Cantacuzino, Georges, 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Cardona, Ramiro and Simmons, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Carter, Gwen, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Caulfield, M., 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Chakraborty, R. 1973 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Chamal, M.C., 1973 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Chance, Norman, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Chiarelli, B, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Choy, E. 1972 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Clark, G.A. (Richards), 1973 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Clark, Maragret, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Churchill, Edmund, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Cloak, Ted, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Cloak, Ted, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Cohn, B, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Colby, B. 1972 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Colllier, D. 1972 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Colorado River Tribe proposal, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Cordwell, Justine, 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Cordwell, Justine, conference on asthetics, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Coutts, P.J.F, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - CRAM, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Cuisinier, J., 1973 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Address, D, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Congress Service Corps, D, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Registration, D, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - D, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - DA-DAT, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - DAV-DE, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - DE LAU-DER, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - DES-DIA, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - DIAS-DOM, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - DOMO-DUC, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - DUG-DUM, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - DUN, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Dahlberg, Albert A. and Graer, 1973-1976 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Damon, Albert, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - David, Ken, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - David, K. undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Degh, Linda, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Delange-Fry, J. 1973 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Decsy, Gyula, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Derkach, Nadia, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Despres, Leon M., 1972-1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Despres, Leon M., 1974 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - de Vos, George, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Diamond, Stanley, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Dorson, Richard M., 1970's (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Dorson, Richard M., post conference, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - du Tuit, Brian M., 1973 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Dundes, Alan, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Doughty, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Dumett, R.E., 1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Dunare, Nicholoas, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Duffy, James, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Dunn, Ethel and Steven, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Durbin, M. 1972 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Address, E, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Congress Service Corps, E, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Registration, E, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - E, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - EA-EL, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - ELL-ERE, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - ERI-EWE (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Ehrenfels, U.R. von, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Elmendorf, Mary, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Elson, Benjamin, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Engel, J, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Everett Michael, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Ewers, J.C., undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Address, F, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Congress Service Corps, F, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Registration, F, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - F, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - FAC-FER, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - FERE-FI, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - FIS-FL, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - FLO-FOS, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - FOU-FRE, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - FREY-FUN, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - FUR, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Fernandez-Guizzetti, G., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Fernandez, James, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Fenton, Kathleen, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Fillmore, Charles, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Fisher, James, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Fitzhugh, W., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Frank, Andre Gunder, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Frankenberg, R, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Freedman, Maurice, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Freedman, Maurice, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Freedman, Maurice, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Freedman, R.L, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Freeman, L.G., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Frese, Herman H., 1972 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Friedmann, N.S. de, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Friedman, S., 1972 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Fuchs, Estelle, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Address, G, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Congress Service Corps, G, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Registration, G, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - G, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - G, 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - GAG-GAM, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - GAN-GAU, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - GAV-GHO, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - GIA-GIV, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - GJ-GOL, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - GOLD-GOT, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - GRA-GRE, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - GREEN-GRO, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - GRO-GU, 1971-1973 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Ganguly, P, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Gast, M., 1972 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Gearing, Fred O., CAE, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Ghabbour, S.I., 1973 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Ghosh, A.K, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Gladwin, Thomas, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Goldberg, H.E., 1972 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Greverus, Ina-Maria, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Gonzalez, Nanci, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Gooch, D.B, 1972-1974 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Gráfik, Imre, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Grollig, F., 1974 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Gruber, Jacob, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Gyula, Ortutay, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Address, H, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Congress Service Corps, H, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Registration, H, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - H, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - HAA-HAM, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - HAN-HAR, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - HAR-HAS, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - HAT-HEI, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - HEL-HIG, 1972-1977 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - HIG-HOL, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - HOL-HUI, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - HUI-HUM, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Hall, Robert, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Hamamsy, Laila Shukry el, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Hamer, John H., 1972 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Hanna, Judith, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Harlan, Jack R., 1974-1979 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Haydu, George G., 1973 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Hennigsen, Gustave, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Henry, Francis, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Hockings, Paul, editor, 1972-1982 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Hockings, Paul, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hofer, T., 1973-1975 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Holbek, B., 1978 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Holloman, R., 1972 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Holloway, Ralph, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Address, I, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Congress Service Corps, I, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Registration, I, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - I, J, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - IBS-IS, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - ISA-ITS, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - ICAES, various, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Institutions R.E.P., 1973 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Isard, Walter, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - ISSC, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Iwanska, A., 1973 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - IWGIA, 1973-1977 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Addresses, J, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Congress Service Corps, I, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - J, registration, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - J-JAC, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - JACK-JAG, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - JAN-JEL, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - JEN-JOH, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - JOL-JUR, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Address, K, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Congress Service Corps, K, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Registration, K, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - K, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - KAB-KAR, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - KAR-KEH, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - KEH-KES, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - KET-KIM, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - KIMM-KIN, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - KNEZ-KOR, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - KOR-KOZ, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - KRA-KUD, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - KUE-KU, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Katz, S.H., 1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Kelly's file, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Kemper, Robert, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Khatri, A.P., 1973 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Kimball, Solon T., 1972 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Kinzer, N.S. and R.P. Schaedel, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Koen, ?, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Kosová, Mária, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Kunstadter, Pete, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Kurais, M. 1973 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Kurta, D.V., 1974 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Address, L, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Congress Service Corps, L, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Registration, L, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - L, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - LAB-LAR, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - LARS-LEA, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - LAU-LOU, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - LEAK-LEIG, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - LEI-LEO, 1972-1973 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - LEV-LIP, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - LIS-LLV, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - LOVE-LY, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Lasker, Gabriel, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Lebeuf, Jean Paul, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Leiderman, P.H., 1971 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Linares, Olga, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Lomax, Alan, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Loos, William, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Address, M, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Congress Service Corps, M, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Registration, M, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - M, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - M-MAB, 1973-1978 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - MAH-MAR, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - MAR-MARW, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - MARW-MAT, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - MAT-MCC, 1972-1973 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - MCCA-MEG, 1972-1975 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - MEI-MIG, 1972-1973 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - MIK-MIT, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - MITCH-MOIA, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - MOL-MOR, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - MORI-MOY, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - MUK-MY, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Machado-Bonet, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Maher, Peter, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Makarius, R., 1973 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Malhotra, K.C., 1973 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Malman, ?, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Maretzki, Tom, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Mead, Margret, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Martin, Paul S. 1972 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Marinov, V. 1973 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Martin, P.S., 1972 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Maruyama, M, 1973-1974 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Maruyama, M, 1973-1976 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Maruyama, M, 1973-1976 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Maruyama, M, 1973-1976 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Maximilian, C., 1971 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - McNeill, W, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - McNeill, W, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Moutan, 1931-1974 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Addresses N, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Congress Service Corps, N, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Registration, N, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - N, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - NA-NAR, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - NAS-NES, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - NET-NEW, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - NEWT-NSU, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - NUK-NZ, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Nash, June, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Nash, M., 1973 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Nelson, Benjamin, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Nettl, Bruno, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Nishimura, Asahitaro, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Nishimura, Asahitaro, 1971-1973 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Nzimiro, I., 1974 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Addresses O, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Congress Service Corps, O, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Registration, O, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - O, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - OB-OLD, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - OLE-OPE, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - OPR-OSI (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - OS-OY, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Addresses P, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Congress Service Corps, P, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Registration, P, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - PA-PAR, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - PAR-PED, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - PEE-PET, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - PET-PIS, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - PIT-POTTS, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - POU-PRI, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - PRIDE-PUT, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Parrott, ?, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Percy, Charles and Adali Stevenson, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Plath, David W., and Ikeda, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Q, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Addresses R, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Congress Service Corps, R, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Registration, R, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - R, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - RAB-RAM, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - RAM-RAU, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - RAUL-RI, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - RID-ROC, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - ROD-ROS, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - ROSE-ROSS, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - RUT-RZ, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Rehfisch, Farnham, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Reynolds, Barrie, Kehoe and Starr, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Riddell, James, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Ritter, Eric, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Ritter, H.H., 1973 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - P. Rodionoff-Peck, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Rohan, C., 1972 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Rossi, Ino, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Rossi-Landi, F., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Rossi-Landi, F., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Rouse, Irving, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Ruby, Jay, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Addresses S, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Congress Service Corps, S, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Registration, S, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - S, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - S-SAL, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - SALO-SAR, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - SAR-SCH, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - SCH, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - SCH-SEA, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - SEAT-SEL, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - SEL-SHA, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - SHAN-SHE, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - SHE-SI, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - SIM, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - SIM, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - SMITH-SUT, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - SOR-SP, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - SPI-STA, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - STA-STE,1973 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - STE-STR, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - STU-SWA, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - SWA-SZ, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Sánchez-Cámara, Florencio, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Sanford, Margret, undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Schema, “Quadrant,” 1976 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Scholte, Robert, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Schwidetsky, J., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Seaton, S. Lee, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Sebeok, Thomas, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Shedlick, E. 1982 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Shimkin, D. 1973 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Shimkin, D. and Peltz, 1973-1978 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Shimkin, D., W. Miller, and H.P. Lundogaarde, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Sibley, Willis E., 1974 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Spiegel, Hedwig, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Silverberg, Jim, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Sliverstein, Michael, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Singh, R. 1974 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Simpson, Ruth D., photos, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Susan E., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Stanley, Andrew B., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Stanley, Samuel, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Stini, William, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Sumi, T. 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Swanson, E. 1974 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Swartz, Ben K., 1975-1978 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Swartz, Ben K., 1972-1974 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Swartz, Ben K., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Szwed, John and Wagner, E., 1972 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Addresses T, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Congress Service Corps, T, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Registration, T, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - T, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - T-TATM 1973 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - TAY-THI, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - THO, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - TSC-TW, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Takla, P.T., 1973 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Takeda, C, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Thomas, Anthony, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Thorensen, T., 1975 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1975-77 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Tkach, Karen, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Topper, M.D., 1973 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Töpper, Sigrid, 1973-1975 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Treide, Dietrich, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Tuttle, Russell, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - U, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - U-V, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Addresses V, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Congress Service Corps, V, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Registration, V, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - VAL, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - VAR-VER, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - VER, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - VON-VU, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Vallee, M.M., 1973 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Vidyarthi, L.P., 1973 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Von Koenigs Wald, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Van Zindren Bakker, E.M., 1973-1974 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Voight, Vilmos, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Vulcanescu, R. (Romanian folk card), 1973 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Addresses W, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Congress Service Corps, W, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Registration, W, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - W, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - WAC, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - WAL-WEB, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - WEI-WIE, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - WIG-WIN, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - WING-WUR, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Wadar, L., 1972 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Wagner, E., 1972 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Watanabe, H., 1973 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Weiner, J.E., 1973 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Werner, Oswald, undated (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Westermeyer, Joseph, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Weissleder, F, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Weissleder, Wolfgang, undated (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Welte, C.R., 1973 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Williams, B.J., 1974 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Thomas, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Thomas, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Wolanski, N. 1973 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Wolf, C.P., 1972 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Wood, H.B., 1973 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - X, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - X, Y, Z, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Addresses, Y, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Congress Service Corps, Y, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Registration, Y, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - YA-YNG, 1972-1973 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - YO-YU, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Yonemura, S., 1973 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Addresses Z, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Congress Service Corps, Z, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Registration, Z, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Z, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Zamora, Mario D., 1973 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Zaongo, B.J. (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Various correspondence, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Various correspondence, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Various correspondence, undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Various correspondence, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Various correspondence, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Various correspondence, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Various correspondence, general inquiries, 1973-1976 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Various correspondence, money request by countries, duplicates, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Various correspondence, Originals of letter from organizers/editor to potential participants, 1973-1974 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Various correspondence, Receipt letter, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Various correspondence, Third World newsletters and unanswered correspondence, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Various correspondence, Third World letters, replies and notes, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Various correspondence, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Various correspondence, A, replacement file, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Various correspondence, A, letters with no follow up, Thank you letters to those intending to participate, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Various correspondence, B, replacement file, undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Various correspondence, B, letters with no follow up, Thank you letters to those intending to participate, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Various correspondence, C, replacement file, undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Various correspondence, D-E, replacement file, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Various correspondence, H, replacement file, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 7)